<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="search_help_html">
 <![CDATA[
<b>To make search screen the default:</b><br/>
On the home screen menu, go into settings.
<p>
<b>Searching can be done several ways:</b><br/>
Note: If you are not looking for a particular place, but for places close by, you should use the filter Current Zip Code, and then from the main report menu
choose All Restaurants from the General Reports section <br/>
</p>
<p>
1)By name - your best bet is to type in as much of the name as you know, and use the \"Containing\" option. If too many results get returned,
 and you know how the name starts, then you can use the "Starts With" option.
</p>
<p>
2)By building number - generally the first information you see on a building\'s door or awning. This is a little tricky,
depending on the borough. In Queens a building number can be 32-47. The data
does not have any hyphens in addresses, so you would need to enter 3247.<br/>
</p>
<p>
3)By street name - often <b>not</b> listed on the building\s door or awning. This is also tricky - it is often preceded by West or East.
 And west and east are expressed in different formats (like west or W). Your best bet is to use the \"Containing\" option and just use a number or name of the street.<br/>
 Examples: For restaurants on West 79th St you would just use 79. The results then can be sorted by zip code to help pinpoint them.<br/>
</p>
<p>
4)By zip code. You should enter a five digit zip code i.e. 10023, but can enter just a part, using contains. If you plan on searching by this zip code often, it is probably better to create a new filter with that zip code.<br/>
<p/>
<p>
5)By phone number. No hyphens are allowed! Your best bet is to use the \"Containing\" option and use the first 3 or the last four digits. If you want to use the
 entire number (without area code) just enter it with consecutive digits. i.e. 555-1234 as 5551234<br/>
<p/>
6)By Cuisine - there are 2 ways to search.<br/><br/>
1) Use the search screen<br/>
This always searches using \"Containing\" because of the way the data is stored. You can enter a type of cuisine you are interested in.
Cuisine descriptions may not be what you expect , so this method may not be so accurate.<br/><br/>
2) Run a report from General data on cuisines.<br/>
This second method is probably better - you get a list of all legitimate cuisines, so you will get results back.
After report runs, press the cuisine you are interested in to see restaurants.
<p/>
 ]]>
 </string>
</resources>