<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="help_help_html">
 <![CDATA[

<b>What scores mean:<br/></b><br/>
A score between 0-13 is an "A"<br/>
A score between 14-27 is a "B"<br/>
A score between 28+ is a "C"<br/><br/>

<b>Sorting</b><br/>
There are two ways to sort.<br/>
1) In results screen, press the SORT menu item. This preference is used for most subsequent reports.<br/>
2) Click one of the column headings. This sort order is not used in subsequent reports.
</p>

<p>
<b>See all violations for a restaurant</b><br/>
    When in results screen, if you tap the restaurant, you will get to the detail screen.
    This screen will show you each inspection by date. By tapping on the inspection date row you will see each violation.
    Critical violations are shown in red text.
</p>
<P>
    <b>Create your own reports</b><br/>
    Go into the Violation Reports section on the home screen  and choose Create Your Own Violation Report.<br/>
    Select a single or multiple violations to include in the report.<br/>
    Run the report.<br/>
    The menu has a Save Report option<br/>
    That report will then be available on the My Saved Reports section.<br/>
    Note: The filter used to re-run that report is the <b>current filter</b>, not the one in effect when the reports was created.<br/>
</p>

<P>
    <b>Create violation watchlist</b><br/>
    When you run a violation report, the detail screen puts an * next to the inspection where that occurred .<br/>
    You can create a violation that always gets marked in the detail screen.<br/>
    On home screen menu select Violation Watchlist.<br/>
    Select violations you want to watch for.<br/>
    Those will now be marked with an X. When you tap on the inspection date row the watched violation will have a light blue background. <br/>
</p>

<P>
    <b>Create your own filter</b><br/>
    From the home screen menu choose Filter - create new filter.<br/>
    Give the filter a name.<br/>
    Enter the zip codes for the filter. Separate the zip codes buy using a comma.<br/>
    Example of zip code filter: 10021,10022,10023<br/>
</p>
<p>
    <b>Hide filters</b><br/>
    If you don\'t want some filters to be visible, you can hide them.<br/>
    From the home page menu choose Filter\\Hide\\Show\\Delete<br/>
    Check filters you want to see.<br/>
    Un-check ones you want to hide.<br/>
</p>
<p>
    <b>Delete a filter</b><br/>
    Long press the filter.<br/>
    Note: Built in filters cannot be deleted, only hidden.<br/>
</p>

<p>
    <b>Use Current Zip Code Filter</b><br/>
    This filter uses Location services on your device to find the current zip code<br/>
    To use this you must have Locations turned on.<br/>
    If you don\'t want Location to be on, and you know your current zip code, you can create a filter with just one zip code, and use that.<br/>
</p>

<p>
    <b>Create a favorites list</b><br/>
    When you are in the detail screen you can choose the Add to Favorites option.<br/>
    Those favorites can be accessed from the Favorite Restaurants section on the home screen.<br/>
    You can delete a favorite by choosing Remove from Favorites in the detail screen.<br/>
 </p>
 ]]>
 </string>

    <!--<p>-->
        <!--<b>Run a report on aggregate data Some reports are:</b><br/>-->
        <!--Get list of establishments closed by the DOHMH.<br/>-->
        <!--Get restaurants based on grades, scores, and violations.<br/>-->
        <!--Find new restaurants.<br/>-->
    <!--</p>-->

</resources>